[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Indiana Jones from the movie of the same name could write and speak this number of languages.", "correct_answer": "27", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "2", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1957 movie about a Venusian invader called Ymir, had special effects done by legend Ray Harryhausen?", "correct_answer": "20 Million Miles to Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Robot Monster", "First Spaceship on Venus", "Forbidden Planet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "No lizard species live on which continent?", "correct_answer": "Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Europe", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are Thylacines marsupials?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actress is not correctly matched with the Woody Allen movie in which she appeared?", "correct_answer": "Meryl Streep - Hannah and Her Sisters", "incorrect_answers": ["Mira Sorvino - Mighty Aphrodite", "Diane Keaton - Manhattan", "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz - Vicky Cristina Barcelona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When starting a diet you have to consume at least this number of calories per day, otherwise you will lose muscle.", "correct_answer": "1200", "incorrect_answers": ["2000", "1000", "1500"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This peanut related sandwich, common in the USA and Canada, is often served with a glass of milk.", "correct_answer": "Peanut butter and jelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Peanut butter and tuna fish", "Grilled cheese and peanuts", "Peanut sauce and broccoli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This U.S. state is home to the Boggy Bayou Mullet Festival, the Winter Strawberry Capital of the World, and The Shark Tooth Capital of the world.", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Mississippi", "Louisiana", "Hawaii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The character of Dennis Nedry gets killed when he stumbles onto a group of this type of dinosaur which spit toxic saliva.", "correct_answer": "Dilophosaur", "incorrect_answers": ["Carnotaur", "Gallimimus", "Velociraptor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the reason for Hummingbirds short life-span?", "correct_answer": "Their fast metabolic rate", "incorrect_answers": ["They have many predators.", "They often get poisoned when feeding on nectar or insects.", "Their small size"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of car did Einstein own while in the USA ?", "correct_answer": "None", "incorrect_answers": ["Buick", "Packard", "Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In their third generation computers flourished, thanks Jack St. Clair Kilbys and Robert Noyces independent invention.  What did they invent?", "correct_answer": "integrated circuit (or microchip)", "incorrect_answers": ["the transistor", "the first computer program", "computer memory"]}]